

OLGA KARACHINTSEVA

10+ Years of Web Development

7+ Technical support and consultancy

5+ Photography/videography/editing

3+ Software development

Certificate in CS & Coding

CONTACTS

<u>okara4inceva@gmail.com</u> <u>+(971)509247454</u>

ABOUT ME

A web technology specialist with over 10 years' experience in web development, content creating and digital marketing,

My areas of expertise include but not limited to Visual Studio, Macromedia and Wondershare products and many others

(HTML/CSS, Java Script, React, Node JS, Git, Mongo DB), Adobe Creative Cloud, including Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom, Capture One. In addition, I have some knowledge in graphic design and familiar with many webdevelopment tools, Google Analytics tools, Different CMS-systems such as NV SmartSite, Celoxis, experience in administration of CMS

I'm very creative, positive and proactive personality, which makes working process with me easy, and fun.

Nationality of Ukraine
Permanent Resident of UAF (husband visa)

SKILLS

GRAPHIC DESIGN

CODING

PHOTOGRAPHY/VIDEOGRAPHY/EDITING

SMM

EDUCATION

COURSES AND CERTEFICATES

MASTERS OF COMPUTER INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND AUTOMATION

2006

COMPUTER DIAGNOSTIC IN HEALTHCARE AND TECHNOLOGIES

Donetsk National Technical University

(Donetsk, Ukraine)

ASTROLABS LEARNING ACADEMY, DUBAI **Computer Science and Coding**, January 2022

ASTROLABS LEARNING ACADEMY, DUBAI Digital Marketing Course, April 2018

ADVANCED GOOGLE ANALYTICS, DUBAI Data Collection, Advanced Analysis and Advanced marketing, May 2019

GOOGLE ADWORDS, DUBAI Search Marketing with Google Ads, June 2019

GOOGLE TAG MANAGER, DUBAI Marketing optimization and Java-script tags, June 2019



EXPERIENCE

Arabic

DIGITAL SPECIALIST, PHOTOGRAPHY GROUP, UAE

WEB TECHNOLOGY CONSULTANT, SE "UKRAINIAN PHARMACEUTICAL QUALITY INSTITUTE" 2021-2022 2009-2017

Consultancy on integration of web technologies Comprehensive content management and technical support of institute web platforms, websites and applications

Successful integration of Pharmaceutical Quality Web Platform in Donetsk region, which was used by 500+ pharmacies across the region

Improving of Institute's customer service rating by 100%

TEAM LEAD AND TECHNICAL SALES, 2008-2009 WEB-LINE STUDIO

Acquisition of new customers
Creating web design for different clients

Preparation of execution plans for development Leading web-development team, providing technical consultation. Promoting of websites (SEO, SMM)

WEB DEVELOPER . XITEX SOFTWARE

2007-2008

Developing of user interface for international clients web sites, HTML, CSS, Java Script coding

Preparing of comprehensive webpage design Generating of frames for the webpages, maps, structure

CONTENT MANAGER, HTML-CODER, AMI LLC

2005-2007

Creating of web page-proofs, models, blocks and templates

Developing of website content with the use of Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Corel Draw